Happy Thanksgiving.
感恩节快乐
Rose, honey, want me to carve that?
罗斯  亲爱的  要我来切吗
Henry, my love, if I let you carve,
亨利  亲爱的  如果我让你来切
we won't eat until tomorrow.
我们到明天都吃不上
I like things to be, you know, precise.
我喜欢一切非常精确
Yes, but we're hungry now.
是的  但我们现在就饿了
- Isn't that right, Kim? - Yeah. Hungry now, Dad.
-对吗  金  -对  我们饿了  爸爸
Mom carves, we eat.
妈妈切  我们能吃
You carve, we wait.
血与肉
All right, savages.
好吧  野蛮人
Yeah, nice try.
想得美
So, this being Thanksgiving,
今天是感恩节
I say we get real
不如我们认真一点
and share something that each of us is thankful for.
分享我们每个人想要感恩的东西
You go first, Rose.
你先来  罗斯
I am thankful that I have you two to come home to
我非常感恩我每天在不怎么友好的天空上
after the nutjobs I deal with across the not-so-friendly skies.
辛苦工作  飞回家后有你们等着我
Your smiling faces make everything okay.
你的笑脸让一切不开心烟消云散
How about you, Kimmy?
你呢  小金
For this.
这一切
For us.
我们
- All right Dad, your turn. - Yeah, your turn.
-好吧  爸爸  轮到你了  -轮到你了
Well, I'm just thankful I didn't have to carve the turkey
还好我不用切火鸡
'cause my stomach's grumbling.
因为我的肚子咕咕叫了
See?
看
But mostly, in all honesty,
但主要来说
I just would never want to lose you two.
我不想失去你们两个
You're the loves of my life.
你们是我一生的挚爱
Cheers to that.
干杯
Love you.
爱你们
Happy Thanksgiving.
感恩节快乐
Sorry, I didn't mean to scare you.
抱歉  不是有意吓你的
I'm off. You take your meds?
我要出去了  你吃药了吗
Come on, Kimberly.
拜托  金伯利
I don't like the way they make me feel.
我不喜欢吃药的感觉
The problem is, they're helping.
问题在于  它们能帮助你
Give me your paw.
把手伸出来
Good girl.
乖
I know you don't want to make a big deal out of this today,
我知道你今天不想好好庆祝
- But? - No, I don't.
-但是  -是的  我不想
Yeah, okay.
好吧
We won't. But your Aunt Jane sent something.
那就不庆祝  但你的简阿姨寄了点东西
It should come today, so it'd probably better to bring it in
今天应该到了  所以最好趁当地的小偷
before the local thieves snatch it from the stoop.
从门廊上偷走前拿进来
- No one's gonna take it. - Really?
-没人会拿的  -真的吗
Tell that to neighbor dude.
告诉那个邻居
He lost a package the other day right off the front porch.
他那天放在门廊上的包裹就被偷了
Same for the old lady two doors down.
住在附近的那位老太太也是
I know what you're trying to do.
我知道你想干什么
You do, don't you?
你知道
Of course you do.
你当然知道
Well, bring it in or not, okay?
随你拿不拿进来
It's not my fault if somebody hijacks it before I get home.
如果有人在我回家前偷走了  那可不是我的错
Bye.
再见
Shit.
该死
Kimberly, this was on the front porch.
金伯利  这个在你们门廊上
Can you take it so I can put my umbrella down?
你能接一下吗  我要收一下伞
Kim?
金
Thank you.
谢谢
What happened?
怎么了
I tried to get the package.
我想去拿包裹
Oh, good for you.
好样的
It's important to push your boundaries.
突破自己非常重要
Maybe we'll try again at the end of the session.
也许我们在今天治疗结束时能再试试
You know, take a stroll down the driveway.
去车道上散散步
Test your limits.
看看你的极限
You turned 17 today. Happy Birthday.
你今天就17岁了  生日快乐
Yeah. No, just another day.
不  只是普通的一天
Same as any other.
和往常一样
How are your days the same?
和往常一样是怎样
Well, I wake up. Um, I kind of get dressed.
我醒过来  换号一度
I do my home-school stuff.
完成了自学作业
Sit around the house. Wait for my dad.
坐在房子里  等我爸爸
Then we eat dinner and watch TV, and go to bed.
然后一起吃晚饭  看电视  上床睡觉
How are you finding the Sertraline?
你觉得舍曲林的效果怎么样
It makes me feel numb.
让我感觉很麻木
Is numb a good thing or a bad thing?
麻木是好事还是坏事
I see your dad is still fixing up the place.
你爸爸好像还是在忙着翻修
Oh, yeah. When he has the time.
是的  他一有空就会做
You know, he's been working a lot lately.
他最近很忙
What do you think your mom would say about all the mess?
你觉得你妈妈看到这一团糟会怎么说
Or was she okay with the home improvement chaos?
还是说她能接受翻修的混乱
Do you, um, want to talk about her today?
你今天想谈谈她吗
It's been almost a year since you lost her.
你已经失去她一年了
And I know that holidays and birthdays
我知道节日和生日
can bring up some really strong emotions.
会激起强烈的情绪
And I also know Thanksgiving was the last holiday
但我也知道感恩节是你和你父亲
that you and your dad got to spend with your mom.
跟你妈妈度过的最后一个节日
No. Just another day,
不  只是普通的一天
the same as any other.
和往常一样
I've worked with many people
我收治过很多
with similar conditions to yours, Kim.
跟你情况类似的病人  金
People with anxiety disorders, panic attacks.
患有焦虑症和恐慌的病人
The ones who cut themselves off from the world.
将自己和世界隔绝的病人
But the difference in your case
但是你的不同在于
is you are a developing, young woman,
你在成长  年轻的女孩
and you need talk to someone real.
你得和真人说说话
Someone present.
你身边的人
Yeah.
嗯
And I have my dad.
我有我爸爸
Yeah. You do.
是的  没错
This is so stupid.
这真是太傻了
Aw, don't be a party pooper.
别这么扫兴
Okay, open your eyes.
好了  睁开眼睛
Go on, make a wish.
来许愿吧
What'd you wish?
你许了什么愿
If I tell you, it won't come true, so...
如果我告诉你  那就不会实现了  所以
That's what they say, whoever "They" Are.
他们都是这么说的  谁知道"他们"都是谁
It was about Mom.
是关于妈妈的
Is that okay?
可以吗
Of course.
当然了
Here goes.
来吧
Looks good, huh?
看起来不错吧
Oh, by the way,
顺便
I know you didn't want me to
我知道你今年不希望
make a big deal out of things this year, but...
我大张旗鼓地庆祝  但是
Go on. Open it.
来吧  打开吧
Yeah.
嗯
It's so pretty.
真漂亮
Try it on.
戴上试试
Here.
给
- All right. - I want to see.
-好  -我想看看
It's pretty.
很漂亮
Thank you.
谢谢你
Happy birthday, sweetheart.
生日快乐  亲爱的
What's on your Thanksgiving menu?
你的万圣节菜单是什么
Tom Elkins, our resident chef, has ideas.
我们的主厨汤姆・埃尔金斯有些主意
All right, well, I'm headed to bed.
好了  我要上床了
All right, sweetheart.
好的  亲爱的
- Thanks for the cake. - Of course.
-谢谢你定的蛋糕  -不用谢
And...And for this.
还有...这个
What'd you get from your aunt?
你的阿姨给你寄了什么
Just some new teas.
一些新茶
White Rose and Keemun,
白玫瑰和祁红
and this book on conquering your fears.
还有一本关于克服恐惧的书
Oh, very subtle, your aunt.
你的阿姨还真是隐晦
Yeah.
嗯
And you got outside to go get it?
你出去拿了进来吗
Right? So that's great.
对吗  很不错
No.
不
Dr. Saunders had to bring it in.
桑德斯医生拿进来的
Well, at least the local thieves were denied, so...
至少挡住了小贼  所以...
Yeah.
嗯
Did you take your meds tonight?
你今晚吃了药吗
Yeah. Yeah.
嗯  嗯
Does she want to send me away?
她想把我送走吗
Who?
谁
Dr. Saunders.
桑德斯医生
I don't know, sometimes I feel like
我不知道  有时候我感觉
she wants to put me away in a hospital or something.
她想把我送到医院什么的
No, honey, no one's sending you anywhere.
不  亲爱的  没人要把你送走
Dr. Saunders is just here to help you through this.
桑德斯医生只是来帮助你好起来
We both are.
我们都是
Okay.
好吧
Go on, get some sleep.
去吧  睡一觉
- Good night. - Night, sweetheart.
-晚安  -晚安  亲爱的
With thirteen days until Turkey Day. Stock up on all...
距离感恩节还有十三天  囤积...
What... ?
怎么...
Kim?!
金
What? What?
怎么了  怎么了
You think you could start helping me with the renovations?
你能帮我进行翻修吗
Why?
为什么
Honestly, because I need the help.
老实说  因为我需要帮助
Please, just help me for the day, yeah?
就今天帮我一把  行吗
Come on.
来
- Very funny. - Oh, sorry.
-很有意思  -抱歉
Yeah, no, that's okay.
不  没关系
There is such a draft coming down from that attic.
阁楼的漏风太严重了
Maybe it's because you just punched a huge hole in the wall.
也许只是因为你在墙上打了个大洞
Yeah? No, it's because I need to put some insulation in.
是吗  不  因为我要往里面装点填料
Mom's to-do list.
妈妈的待办清单
Always after me to get 'er done, so...
总是在我做完后列出来的  所以
high time I did.
现在我该做了
Can I?
我能试试吗
Oh, yeah, sure.
当然了
Cool.
好的
Put that on. For the plaster dust.
戴上这个  挡石膏粉尘
- These, too. - Oh. Thanks.
-还有这些  -谢谢
I can see all the way up to the top of the house.
我能看到屋顶
- Yeah? - It's crazy.
-是吗  -太疯狂了
I was thinking, um,
我在想
Thanksgiving I could make a turkey, pick up some sides.
感恩节  我可以做个火鸡  做点配菜
Course, it wouldn't, you know...
因为  可能不会
Wouldn't be as good as your mom's, but...
不会有你妈妈做的那么好
we could try and make something special out of it.
我们可以试试  做点特殊的菜
Sure.
好啊
If you think you can handle it.
如果你觉得你可以搞定
Well, if you give me a hand, you bet.
如果你能帮我的话  那当然了
Yeah. If you want to, I'd... Yeah, I'd like that.
如果你想要的话  我可以...行啊
All right, good. Thanksgiving dinner at home.
很好  那就在家吃感恩节晚餐
Great.
很好
So, do you, um, have any goals?
你有什么目标吗
Like what?
比如说呢
What would you like to do for a living,
如果你什么都能做
if you could do anything?
你愿意以什么为生呢
I don't know.
我不知道
Something with travel maybe.
能旅游的工作吧
Travel?
旅游
That's interesting considering...
很有意思  因为...
Must be a real headache
天天活在这种
living with this in the background every day.
背景音下肯定很难熬吧
I'm used to it.
我习惯了
Okay, my dad knows what he's doing.
我爸爸知道自己在做什么
Travel?
旅游
Isn't that what your mother used to do?
这不是你妈妈经常做的事吗
She was a travel agent?
她是一名旅行社代理人
Flight attendent.
乘务员
Waitress in the sky.
空中服务员
That's what she used to call it.
她经常是这么自称的
I am...
我...
I'm not here to judge you,
我不是要批评你
and the last thing I want to do is upset you.
我也根本不想让你失望
But I can't help if you keep pretending
但是如果你一直假装没有问题
that there are no problems here.
那我是帮不了你的
What do you want me to say?
你要我怎么说
Your mother's death was a terrible loss to endure at your age.
你这个年纪失去母亲是一件非常可怕的事
It's one thing when a person dies before their time,
英年早逝是一回事
but it is another thing for them to be taken.
但年少痛失亲人又是另一回事
No, you don't know what you're talking about.
不  你不知道自己在说什么
Only because you won't talk to me.
只是因为你不愿意和我说
Because I'm tired of answering your questions!
因为我厌倦回答你的问题了
Okay? Just leave me alone!
好吗  别管我了
Say I did.
假设我走了
Say I left you alone and didn't come back.
假设我丢下你  再也没回来
Then what?
然后呢
I mean, do you think you'd be better or worse?
你觉得你会好转  还是会恶化
This whole thing is about trust, Kimberly.
这一切的重点就是要信任  金伯利
You need to trust me.
你需要信任我
People beat themselves up
人们经常会因为
all the time over the most awful things.
各种可怕的事而怪自己
Things that they had no control over.
他们无法控制的事
And it's common after a traumatic experience to blame yourself.
遭遇创伤后  怪自己也是很常见的事
Why would I do that?
我为什么要那么做
I didn't kill her.
又不是我杀死了她
Of course you didn't.
你当然没有
But you need to acknowledge what happened.
但你需要承认发生的事
I can acknowledge it.
我可以承认
Okay, some sick bastard murdered my mother
好吧  一个混蛋杀死了我妈妈
and dumped her body in a vacant lot.
把她的尸体扔在了一片空地上
There, I said it.
好了  我说出来了
Am I cured now?
我现在治愈了吗
I think you're afraid
我觉得你很害怕
because the man who did this was never caught.
是因为犯下这些罪行的人没有被抓住
And maybe that's why you don't want to leave.
也许这就是为什么你不想离开
Well, would you?
换做是你呢
I'm safe here.
我在这里很安全
I'm safe alone with my dad.
我和我爸爸一起就很安全
And what if something happens to him?
万一他出什么事呢
You can't stay in here forever.
你不能永远待在这里
The world is out there.
外面有大千世界
You hide in here, and you let whoever took your mom away win.
你躲在这里  杀死你妈妈的人就赢了
Win?
赢
God, you make it sound like a game.
天啊  你说得好像一切都是一场游戏
Couldn't help overhearing the session.
我听到了你们的治疗
Got a little heated, huh?
气氛有点紧张啊
Well, confrontational forms of therapy
对抗的治疗形式
tend to get patients worked up.
能够让病人振作起来
I'm used to it.
我习惯了
She's got the same fire her mom had.
她和她妈妈有一样的活力
Kimberly's, uh, not making very good progress, Mr. Tooms.
金伯利的治疗效果不大好  图姆斯先生
She just needs to spend more time with you.
她只是需要再多和你待一段时间
Has Kimberly ever displayed physical aggression toward you?
金伯利有没有对你表现出肢体上的冲撞
Or herself?
或者伤害她自己
No. She wouldn't do that.
不  她不会这么做的
Was she ever angry with your wife?
她有没有冲你妻子发过火
With Rose? No!
和罗斯吗  没有
Never. I mean, no more than the usual mother/daughter spat.
从来没有  不过是普通的母女争吵
Why?
怎么了
Well, I'm just trying to get a better picture of Kimberly
我只是想更加了解
and her mental state leading to the onset of the anxiety.
金伯利焦虑发作的具体情况
No, she couldn't... couldn't hurt anybody.
不  她不可能  不可能伤害任何人
Especially not her mother. Not on purpose.
特别是她母亲  至少绝对不会故意
You know, Henry, it's easy to miss things
亨利  当你身为一名家庭成员
when you're emotionally enrolled with a family member.
你很容易会忽略掉一些事
- It's cliche. - Yeah, okay, Doc.
-这是老生常谈了  -好的  医生
- But parents are often the last to know. - Yeah.
-但是父母总是最后一个知道的  -嗯
So, keep an eye out for extreme behaviors.
所以一定要注意她的极端行为
Now, it could be a sign of the medication,
可能是需要加大用药的迹象
but it could be a sign of a deeper pathology.
也可能是病情加重的表现
Extreme behaviors?
极端行为
Well, Kimberly's angry,
金伯利很愤怒
and anger can manifest itself in many ways.
愤怒能表现在多方面
Like what?
比如说呢
Delusional, obsessive, paranoid.
妄想  强迫  偏执
Look, spending as much time as she does alone,
尽可能一个人待着
refusing to acknowledge what happened to her...
拒绝承认自己身上发生的事
No. Look, um, Kimberly's been through a lot.
不  听着  金伯利经历了很多事
She'll pull through this. She will.
她会熬过来的  会的
You're grieving,
你很悲伤
And I know it's not easy. For either of you,
我知道这对你们俩来说都不容易
but if Kimberly doesn't confront what happened,
但如果金伯利无法面对发生的事
this house will turn from a sanctuary into a cell.
这间房子只会从一个圣所变成一个监狱
This is her home.
这是她的家
It's not a prison.
不是一个监狱
Henry, please.
亨利  拜托
You're coddling her when you should be coaxing her out,
你这样太由着她了  你应该让她出来
breaking the cycle that's keeping her inside.
打破将她关在里面的怪圈
I know how to raise my own daughter.
我知道怎么养我的女儿
I'll see you next week.
下周见
Please, just, um, think about what I said.
拜托  想想我说的建议
Sorry.
抱歉
For what?
为什么
For being a bitch.
表现这么差
Oh honey. You're doing the best you can, all right?
亲爱的  你经历了  好吗
- Yeah. - You okay?
-嗯  -你没事吧
Well, yeah.
嗯
I'm gonna head down to O'Malley's, get a beer with the guys.
我要去奥麦利酒吧  和他们喝几杯
Okay.
好的
When I get back, we can watch a movie, pig out on ice cream.
等我回来  我们能一起看电影挖冰淇淋
- Great. - All right. Be good.
-太好了  -好  乖乖的
- Yeah. You, too. - All right.
-嗯  你也是  -好
A teenager from Encino, California,
来自加利福尼亚恩西诺的失踪少年
is still missing after a one-week search
在经过一周搜索后仍然不见踪影
has failed to turn up any new leads or witnesses.
也并没有找的新的线索或者目击证人
Police suspect Sophie Taylor was abducted near her Encino home.
警方怀疑索菲・泰勒是在恩西诺自己家附近被诱拐
At a press conference earlier this morning,
在今早举办的发布会上
her parents made an appeal for information
她的父母恳求公众提供
concerning their daughter's disappearance.
关于他们失踪女儿的信息
I just want everyone to know
我只希望大家知道
what a beautiful, kind, and wonderful person my daughter is.
我女儿是个美丽  善良  优秀的人
If you're watching this, Sophie,
如果你在看  索菲
we love you very much.
我们非常爱你
We just want to know that you're okay
我们只想知道你没事
and for you to come home.
希望你能回家
We're appealing to anyone who knows any information
希望任何知道有关
regarding Sophie Taylor's whereabouts
索菲・泰勒去向的人
to contact this number immediately.
失踪少女  索菲・泰勒
Oh, my God.
天啊
In national news, the President is once again under fire
国内新闻  总统继续因为他
for his continual attack
持续攻击...
Okay.
好吧
Shit.
该死
Oh, you're still up. I thought you'd be in bed by now.
你还醒着  我以为你现在已经睡了
Oh, I thought we had movie night.
我们今晚不是要看电影吗
Yeah, it just took a little longer than I planned.
是的  我没想到这么晚才能回来
Lend a hand?
帮我一把
Oh, sure.
当然了
Is it cold outside?
外面很冷吗
Cold? No, well, it's a little chilly in the van.
不冷  车里有点凉
What have you been up to?
你都在干什么呢
Just watching TV.
看看电视
Anything good?
有好看的吗
No, nothing really.
不  没什么好看的
Surfing mostly.
主要是冲浪节目
You're bluffing, Mr. Bigelow.
你在唬我  比格罗先生
I don't know what you're after, but you're trying to trick me.
我不知道你想干什么  但是你想骗我
Mrs. Phillips, can you tell me...
菲利普太太  你能告诉我
You're not hungry?
你不饿吗
Uh, just lost my appetite, I guess.
就是没胃口了
For ice cream?
冰淇淋的胃口
Well, I'll clean up.
我来打扫
- Shit! - Easy there, jumpy.
-该死  -慢点  小冒失鬼
Sorry.
抱歉
No, it's all right.
不  没关系
- No, I can clean it up. - Let me get it.
-不  我能清理干净  -让我来
- Careful. - Ow, shit.
-小心点  -该死
Damn, I told you to be careful.
该死  我要你小心点的
Come on, let me see.
来  让我看看
- Let me see. - It's fine.
-让我看看  -没事
It's fine.
没事的
Let me see.
让我看看
No, it's not too deep, but, yeah, we should definitely wash up.
不  伤口不深  但我们得好好洗干净
Come on.
来
Yeah. Okay.
好了
I got blood on you.
我把血弄到你身上了
I don't mind.
我不介意
There we go.
好了
Yeah, that's the least I can do.
我至少还能这样帮帮你
Thanks.
谢谢
Hey, Dad?
爸爸
Hey, happy Thanksgiving, sweetheart.
感恩节快乐  亲爱的
Yeah.
嗯
I have to go out for a bit today.
我今天得出去一下
I left instructions for the turkey.
我会给你留下做火鸡的菜单
I think you just kind of bake it all day,
你就花一整天来好好烤
baste every once in a while.
隔一段时间来涂点料
Can you handle that for us?
你能做到吗
Uh, yeah, sure, um...
好的
Hey, where did you get my birthday present?
我的生日礼物是哪里买的
At a jewelry shop in the Valley. Why?
小巷里的一家首饰店  怎么了
Are you sure it's not second-hand?
你确定这不是二手的吗
What?
什么
Well, it's tarnished. See?
这都暗了  看到了吗
- Tarnished? - Yeah.
-暗了  -对
Didn't see that when I bought it,
我买的时候没注意到
but, um, it's a manufacturing flaw, I suppose.
但估计只是一点小瑕疵
It happens.
常有的事
So then maybe you can exchange it for a new one?
那你能不能去换个新的
It's the only one they had in stock. Sorry, Kim.
他们只有这一个了  抱歉  金
Here, eat your breakfast.
来  把早餐吃了
Before it gets cold.
别放凉了
Thanks.
谢谢
Disgusting.
真恶心
Oh, shit.
该死
Is that... blood?
那是...血吗
Oh, my God.
天啊
Hey, Aunty Jane? It's Kimberly.
简阿姨  我是金伯利
I know it's the holidays,
我知道今天是万圣节
but I really, really have to stay with you for a few days.
但我真的需要去你那里住几天
Um, I'll explain more when I see you.
等我见到你后会向你解释的
Just give me a call back. Okay, bye.
请回电  好的  再见
Okay, come on, Kimberly.
好的  加油  金伯利
Come on, come on, come on.
加油  加油  加油
You can't stay here, Kim.
你不能待在这里  金
Okay.
好吧
It's just the sun.
只不过是太阳
That's just some birds.
那只是一些鸟
You're gonna be okay.
你会没事的
I'm home!
我回来了
Think I found the last pumpkin pie.
我觉得我买到了最后一块南瓜派
How'd it go with the turkey today?
今天火鸡做得怎么样
You didn't even set the ta--
你连桌子都...
What is this, Dad?
这是什么  爸爸
They're nothing for you to worry about.
你不用担心这些
Did you steal them?
这些是你偷的吗
What were you even doing in the attic?
你去阁楼干什么
I just wanted to see what you've been doing.
我只是想去看看你都在干什么
See what? I've been working on the house.
看什么  我一直在装修房子
Honestly, Kim, I think you have to stop
老实说  金  我觉得你该停止
with these wild assumptions.
这些无端的猜测
I can hear you moving around up there.
我可以听到你在上面走来走去
At night.
大半夜
Is this what you've been doing?
你就在干这种事吗
Hiding these?
藏着些东西吗
Dad!
爸爸
I'm allowed to have my own private things, Kim.
我可以有我的隐私  金
But why would you hide them like that?
但你为什么要这样把它们藏起来
- Damn it, Kim! It's gonna be dry! - Dad?
-该死  金  这样会干的  -爸爸
See, this is why your mother and I never got you a cat.
所以我和你妈妈不给你买猫
Why would you hide them in Mom's old work bag?
你为什么把这些藏在妈妈以前工作用旅行箱里
I miss your mom, Kim.
我很想你的妈妈  金
Same as you. I try to hide it,
和你一样  我想要隐藏
but sometimes I just need to spend some time alone
但有时候我只是需要和
with the few remaining pieces that she left behind.
她的遗物单独待一会
Pieces that are mine. Just mine.
属于我的东西  只属于我
Kim?
金
Look sweetheart, I'm sorry if it upset you,
亲爱的  我很抱歉这让你很难过
but Dad's not perfect.
但爸爸不完美
There's blood on this.
这上面有血
That's paint.
那是涂料
You're not gonna answer that?
你不接吗
No, not right now.
不  现在不接
Are you taking your meds?
你吃药了吗
What?
什么
Well, Dr. Saunders said there might be side effects--
桑德斯医生说可能会有一些副作用
erratic behavior, paranoia.
激进的行为  妄想
It's not the med-- Don't turn this around on me!
不是因为药  别把矛头对准我
Kim, I gotta be honest with you. You're acting paranoid again.
金  说实话  你现在又有妄想的表现了
- Over nothing. Really nothing! - Just stop lying!
-明明什么事都没有  -别再撒谎了
Don't take that tone with me! I am still your father!
别对我大呼小叫  我还是你爸爸
Did you kill her?
你杀了她吗
What?! Who?
什么  谁
Sophie Taylor.
索菲・泰勒
This is her necklace, isn't it?
这是她的项链  对吗
Well, isn't it?!
不是吗
Come on, Dad, the truth.
拜托  爸爸  真相
Not gonna tell the truth? Fine.
不说实话  好吧
They're the same.
这是一样的
Same mark.
一样的挂坠
Yeah, I talked to the store.
我问过店里了
Yeah, but they said it's a style.
但他们说这是流行
Distressed, they called it.
他们说这叫"痛苦"
Okay.
好吧
Well, what about these?
那这些呢
Who did they belong to?
这些都是谁的
They belonged to your mother.
这些都是你妈妈的
Pieces she picked up from flights over the years.
她这些年在飞机上找到的首饰
She should've turned them in
她应该上交的
to lost and found or whatever, of course, but...
给失物招领处什么的  但是
you know, your mom was not perfect.
你妈妈并不完美
I'm not perfect.
我并不完美
You're not perfect.
你并不完美
I didn't want to tell you in case you...
我不想告诉你  万一你...
freaked out.
抓狂了呢
But that doesn't explain--
但那不能解释
You're turning into her, do you know that?
你正在变成她  你知道吗
Neurotic and paranoid until the end.
最后会变成妄想症和神经质
Did you kill her?
你杀了她吗
No, Kim.
不  金
Oh, my God, did you kill Mom?
天啊  你杀了妈妈吗
The person who killed your mother
杀死你妈妈的人
is still out there.
仍然在逃
Or he's been here with me
或者他一直以来
the whole time.
都和我一起
Kim, come on, now!
金  拜托
Kim, wait.
金  等等
- Kim. - No.
-金  -不
Kim, open up. Come on now. This is silly.
金  开门  拜托  这太蠢了
I didn't do anything wrong.
我没做错什么
Kimberly? I love you.
金伯利  我爱你
Now open up.
赶紧开门
Whatever you're doing in there,
不管你在里面做什么
just don't hurt yourself, sweetheart.
不要伤到你自己  亲爱的
Kimberly?!
金伯利
I said open this damn door!
赶紧给我把门打开
Open the damn door!
把门打开
All right.
好吧
I'm gonna count to three, and then I'm coming in.
我数到三  我就进来了
One...
一
Two...
二
Three!
三
I'm calling the police!
我报警了
911 Emergency. How may I direct your call?
911急救  请问有什么需要的
Um, it's my dad.
是我爸爸
I think he's trying-- He's trying to get in my room.
我觉得他想  他想进入我的房间
Okay, okay. Can I take your name please?
好的  请告诉我你叫什么名字
Kimberly Tooms.
金伯利・图姆斯
All right, Kimberly, can you give me your location?
好的  金伯利  能告诉我你住在哪里吗
Uh, 14 Victoria Avenue, Echo Park.
维多利亚大道14号  回声公园
What's the nature of your emergency?
你的紧急情况是怎么回事
You said your dad is trying to get into your room?
你说你的爸爸想进入你的房间
- Yeah, I think he's hurt someone. - Who has he hurt?
-我觉得他在追杀人  -他在追杀谁
I don't know. Can you just send help?
我不知道  你能派人来帮忙吗
I'm dispatching a police unit to your address now.
我正在派一队警员前往你的地址
Is there a lock on your door?
你的门上有锁吗
Yeah, I already locked it.
嗯  我已经锁上了
That's good. Stay there. Help is coming.
很好  待在里面  救援马上来
I think he's coming back.
我觉得他回来了
Kimberly?
金伯利
Kimberly, stay on the line.
金伯利  别挂电话
Stand back from the door, sweetheart.
别离门太近  亲爱的
Just a second!
稍等一下
- No! - Almost in!
-不  马上进来了
Kimberly!
金伯利
No, no, no, no, no, no, no!
不不不不不
What are you doing? Get away from there!
你在干什么  赶紧下来
- No! No! - What are you doing?! Come on! Stop it!
-不  不  -你干什么  下来
I'm not gonna hurt you! I'm not gonna hurt you!
我不会伤害你  我不会伤害你
I said that's enough!
够了
Okay?
好吗
Are you calm now?
你冷静下来了吗
I asked you a question, Kim! Are you calm now?!
我问你  金  你冷静下来了吗
Can we please just talk about
我们能不能好好
this quietly and sensibly? Can we do that?
安静地谈谈这些事  可以吗
It's just that I've been under a lot of stress lately.
我只是最近压力太大了
That's all.
仅此而已
This just happens to everybody.
每个人都会这样
Who did you call?
你给谁打了电话
No one.
没谁
Oh, sweetheart.
亲爱的
I really wish you hadn't done that.
真希望你没有这么做
It's okay. We'll sort this whole mess out.
没事  我们能解决的
So, what are we gonna do now?
我们现在该怎么办
Police are on their way,
警察在来的路上了
so you're gonna have a lot of explaining to do.
你有很多事要向他们解释
So do you.
你也是
So, who's gonna take care of you when I'm not around?
我不在了  谁来照顾你呢
Did you think of that?
你有没有考虑过呢
No, without me, there's no roof over your head.
不  没有我  你就没有容身之处
A roof, which I'd like to point out,
没有容身之所  我必须提醒你
that you're too afraid to get out from under anyway.
你甚至都不敢走出去
Probably just wind up in a damn nut house.
可能只会流落到精神病院
Rubber rooms and straightjackets for you.
让你进橡胶房  穿连体衣
You're the one who needs help.
你才是需要帮助的人
I didn't do anything.
我什么毒没做
You're acting paranoid. Delusional.
你才是有妄想  出现幻觉
That's not true.
不是这样的
All right, you listen to me.
好吧  听我说
Are you sure?
你确定吗
Sweetheart, you've known me your whole life.
亲爱的  你最了解我了
I've always been there for you.
我一直都在你身边
I never hit you.
我从没打过你
I never hurt you.
我从没伤害过你
Barely even raise my voice.
基本没大声说过话
Have I?
是吗
Because I love you, Kimberly. You mean everything to me.
因为我爱你  金伯利  你对我来说就是一切
But what about the jewelry?
那这些首饰呢
I mean, I just don't believe it was Mom's.
我不相信那是妈妈的
Doesn't matter what you believe.
你相信什么并不重要
I'm sorry you found it.
我很抱歉被你找到了
I really am.
真的
It hasn't been easy.
这一直很难过
What happened to your mother is an awful thing,
你母亲的遭遇的确很可怕
but you can't blame me for that.
但你不能怪我
I know you hate me, I get it.
我知道你恨我  真的
I have been somewhat remote lately.
我最近的确对你有点疏远
But I've had so much on my mind.
但我有太多事要操心
I just wanted this first
我只是希望这第一个
Thanksgiving without your mother to be...
没有你母亲的感恩节能...
I don't know, somehow...
我也不知道  你能...
okay for you.
觉得可以
For us.
我们都能
But am I guilty of being a murderer?
但我是一名杀人犯吗
How can you even think that?
你怎么能有这种想法
So when those police officers show up,
等那些警察来了
you need to be certain of that.
你必须要明确这一点
You need to know in here,
你这里要明白
and you need to know in here.
你这里也要明白
Without any doubt.
毋庸置疑
Otherwise, you'd destroy what's left of our family.
不然  你就会毁掉我们家庭剩余的一切
So, now
那么现在
do you feel that you're one hundred percent positive
你觉得你百分百确认
that I am who you think I am?
我是你认为的那种人吗
Good.
很好
Then when the police officers do show up, don't say anything.
那么等警察们来了  什么都别说
It's the medication
是药物
and your condition that's warping your thinking.
和你的病情搅乱了你的大脑
They'll understand.
他们会明白的
Evening, sir.
晚上好  先生
I'm Officer Foster,
我是福斯特警官
this is Officer Banks, LAPD.
这是班克斯警官  我们是洛杉矶警局的
Evening.
晚上好
We received a 911 call from this address in the last half hour.
我们半小时前接到这个地址的一个报警电话
A young woman said she was in distress.
一名年轻女子称自己有麻烦
Yeah, that would be my daughter.
那应该是我的女儿
- Are you the homeowner? - Yes.
-你是屋主吗  -是的
And your name?
你叫什么名字
Henry Tooms.
亨利・图姆斯
Mr. Tooms, on the basis of this call,
图姆斯先生  根据那通电话
we have just cause to enter your property to conduct a search
我们有正当理由进入你们的住所进行搜查
and to interview both you and your daughter.
并对你和你的女儿进行问话
Do you have a problem with this?
你有什么意见吗
No, please, come in.
没有  请进
Apologies for the mess.
抱歉屋里很乱
Renovations.
翻修
Are you Kimberly? Did you make the 9-1-1 call?
你是金伯利吗  是你报警的吗
- Yeah. - It's a bit embarrassing, actually.
-是的  -其实有点尴尬
Kim just overreacted.
金反应过度了
Mr. Tooms, we're gonna need you
图姆斯先生  请你暂时
to step outside the room for a minute.
离开这个房间
Why?
为什么
I'm gonna need talk to Kimberly alone,
我要单独和金伯利谈谈
and my partner, she's gonna take
我的搭档会去厨房
your statement in the kitchen there.
给你做笔录
All right.
好吧
After you.
请
I'm Officer Banks.
我是班克斯警官
Can I get you anything?
有什么需要我帮助的吗
No.
不
Are you injured?
你受伤了吗
So your dad's renovating, huh?
你爸爸最近在翻修
Oh. Um, yeah.
对
It's been taking a while.
已经忙活了一阵了
- May I? - Sure.
-我能坐吗  -好的
- Ooh! No, no. - Sorry.
-不  不  -抱歉
No, no, I got it. It's mine.
不  不  我来吧  这是我的
Kimberly, I'm gonna need you to tell me
金伯利  我需要你告诉我
what happened here tonight.
今晚发生了什么
Think you can do that for me?
你可以告诉我吗
You must get a lot of bogus domestic calls at the holidays.
节假日肯定接到很多报警电话吧
What makes you say that?
你为什么这么说
Well, I just mean, families together, tempers flare.
就是合家团聚  气氛高涨
Next thing you know,
接下来
Uncle Joe stabs Cousin Lou with a fork kinda thing.
乔叔叔可能就用叉子什么的捅了卢侄子
It happens.
有可能
Kimberly, your dad's not here right now. It's just you and me.
金伯利  你爸爸现在不在  只有我和你
You made the call for a reason.
你打电话肯定是有原因的
Just tell me what-- what made you pick up the phone.
告诉我你为什么要打电话
Nothing.
没什么
He's right. I overreacted.
他说得对  我反应过度
So, your daughter's prone to this kind of behavior?
字幕
No, she's...
不  她
She's such a good girl. It's just been a tough year.
她是个好姑娘  今年对她来说太难了
Her mother was murdered last year.
她的母亲去年被杀了
- Rose Tooms? - Yeah.
-罗斯・图姆斯  -是的
Sorry for your loss.
节哀顺变
Yeah, well, the cops haven't found the guy yet.
警察还没抓到这家伙
So you're suggesting this is the reason she made that call?
你是说她是因为这个才打电话的吗
Officer, my daughter's been a shut-in since this happened.
警官  我女儿从那时起就一直闭门不出
She can't even leave the house.
她甚至都没法离开这房子
She'll have a panic attack when the front door opens.
只要前门一打开  她就会恐慌发作
I can't unlatch a window without her getting dizzy.
我打开窗户  她都会头晕
She's taking this medication for, uh...
她一直在吃药治疗...
Agoraphobia?
广场恐怖症
Yep.
没错
- Are you seeking treatment for that? - My dad got me a therapist.
-你有在进行治疗吗  -我爸爸帮我找了治疗师
We have sessions at home.
我们在家里治疗
Can you tell me the name of your doctor?
你的医生叫什么名字
Dr. Helen Saunders.
海伦・桑德斯医生
And would it be okay with you if I contacted her?
我可以联系她吗
I haven't been around as much.
我最近都没怎么在家
And work's been, like, crazy.
工作真是忙坏了
Trying to support the both of us.
为了赚钱供我们俩生活
Uh, she's just lonely and angry.
她只是太孤单和愤怒
I told her off earlier, she ran upstairs.
我之前说了她几句  她就跑到楼上去了
Teenagers.
青少年
Why'd you tell her off?
你为什么要说她
Well, the house is just--
这房子...
it's all over the place right now, you know?
最近实在是太乱了
All right.
好吧
She went up to the attic, and I told her-- Well, I don't know.
她上了阁楼  我告诉她  我也不知道
She was up there to see some of her mom's old stuff,
她上去看到了一些她妈妈以前的东西
so, like, you know.
于是  你懂的
But she practically broke her neck, so I got--
但她都快摔断脖子了  所以我
I just-- I lost it,
我  我失控了
so she ran to her room, wouldn't come out.
她就跑回了房间  不愿意出来
You know, I raised my voice with her a bit.
我的声音就有点大
I don't think she was used to it.
我觉得她一时接受不了
She called you guys.
她就给你们打了电话
Mr. Tooms, domestic abuse is a serious issue.
图姆斯先生  家庭暴力是非常严重
We get a lot of calls on it.
我们经常会接到这种报警
So I have to ask...
所以我必须要问你
have you ever hit her before?
你以前打过她吗
No. Never.
不  从来没有
He's never raised his hand to you in any way?
他从来没有对你动过手吗
No. I was just mad.
不  我就是太生气了
This is-- I shouldn't have said anything.
这...我不该那样说的
I don't--
我不...
I don't want him to get in any trouble.
我不想给他惹上麻烦
I understand that. He's your dad.
我明白  他是你爸爸
He-- He hasn't done anything wrong.
他  他没做错什么
Are you sure there's nothing else you want to tell me?
你确定你没有别的事想告诉我了吗
Yeah, I'm sure.
我确定
Okay then, I think we're done here.
那  我觉得我们问完了
Yeah, it appears so.
看起来是的
According to your dad,
据你爸爸所称
this was all some sort of misunderstanding.
这一切都只是一个误会
- Is that correct? - I'm sorry.
-对吗  -对不起
In that case,
既然如此
I'm gonna have to caution you against wasting police time.
我需要警告你下次不得再浪费警方的事件
We're only to be called in cases of genuine emergencies.
只有在真正出事时才能打给我们
Do you understand?
明白了吗
Yes, I'm sorry.
嗯  我很抱歉
All right, if there's nothing else...
好了  如果没有别的事了
Okay, then we'll head out.
好的  那我们走了
Love you.
爱你
Thanks for coming just the same.
还是谢谢你们的到来
- You have a good night. -Thank you.
-祝你们晚安  -谢谢
Hey, hold on one second.
稍等一下
Hey, listen, if there's anything that you want to talk about
听着  如果你有什么你觉得
that you feel like you can't talk about here,
你不能在这里说的事
call me direct, okay?
直接打给我
- Okay. - Anything at all.
-好的  -什么事都行
Thanks.
谢谢
Night. Thanks again.
晚安  再次谢谢你
Happy holidays.
节日快乐
Go to bed. I'll fix your door in the morning.
上床  我明早修你的门
You were in my room.
你进过我房间
How would you feel if I went through your personal things?
我如果翻你的私人物品  你会怎么想
Should I be disappointed?
我应该感到失望
Angry?
生气
Or mad at myself for not bringing you up right?
还是气我自己没把你教育好
I hurt myself.
我伤到了
Give me that.
给我
Why?
为什么
Because it's mine.
因为这是我的
This wasn't in your collection.
这不在你的收藏里
- Just give it to me. - You know what's weird?
-给我  -你知道最奇怪的是什么吗
What?
什么
All those girls that went missing?
不见的那些女孩
They all kinda look the same.
她们看起来都很像
They kinda look like Mom.
她们都有点像妈妈
This whole thing's getting out of hand.
这一切都开始失控了
I love you, and I loved your mom, Kim.
我爱你  我爱你妈妈  金
Our family, it was and is the most important thing to me.
我们的家庭对我来说是最重要的事
The night your mom disappeared, we fought.
你妈妈失踪那晚  我们吵了架
Rose had a last-minute schedule change. Again.
罗斯又一次在最后关头改变了计划
And I was tired of it.
我受够了
I was tired of not being first.
我受够不被她放在第一位
Of you and me not being first.
我和你不被放在第一位
Do I regret every word of that fight?
我后悔我们吵架时我说的话吗
Yes! Every minute, every second of every day.
当然了  每天每一分每一秒
But when the cops found your mom's body,
但是当警察们找到了你妈妈的尸体
please, you gotta believe me, my heart broke forever.
拜托  相信我  我的心永远碎了
I wish I could take those words and take the anger out of them
我也希望能收回那些话  收回那些怒气
and replace it with compassion and patience.
用热忱和耐心来取代
Which is what I'm doing now.
我现在就在这么做
Do you think I wanna lose you?
你觉得我想失去你吗
Do you think I'm gonna let Dr. Saunders have you committed?
你觉得我会让桑德斯医生让你住院吗
Kimberly, no!
金伯利  不
All I have is us!
我只有我们了
Kim, please, please just give it to me,
金  拜托  给我吧
go to sleep, and everything will be better in the morning.
去睡觉吧  明天一切都会好的
Kimberly.
金伯利
Kim.
金
- Put that away! - How many?
-收起来  -多少人
You're gonna hurt yourself.
你会伤到你自己的
How many?
多少人
This is exactly what Dr. Saunders warned me about.
桑德斯医生之前就提醒过我
She said your medication might trigger aggression.
她说你的药物可能会让你有攻击性
She told me to look for this, and I didn't listen.
她要我小心  我没有听
If you hurt yourself, if you hurt me, you'll be locked up.
如果你伤到了自己  伤到我  你就会被关起来
Stay where you are, please.
不要动
I wasn't the only one who fought with her that night!
那天晚上不仅仅只有我和她吵了架
You don't remember that, do you?
你不记得了  对吗
You don't remember how angry you were at her that night.
你不记得你那晚有多么愤怒
- That's not true. - It's not?
-不是这样的  -不是吗
- That's not true. - Are you sure?
-不是这样的  -你确定吗
- Go! Leave! - Kim, it's not what you think!
-你走吧  -金  不是你想的这样
- Just trust me for once! - Trust you?
-信我这一次  -信你
Why would I trust someone who's cheating on my dad?
我为什么要信背叛我爸爸的人
- I'm not! - You leave him. You leave me.
-我没有  -你离开了他  离开了我
You leave us! Leave!
你离开了我们  走吧
- And don't bother coming back here! - Kim!
-别再回来了  -金
Kimberly, just give me the knife
金伯利  把刀给我
before something happens you can't take back.
趁一切还没到不可挽回的地步
Kimberly.
金伯利
- Put that down. - I said stay away from me.
-放下  -我说别靠近我
Stay back!
后退
No.
不
No, no, no, no, no, no, no!
不不不不不
Stop. No, no, no!
住手  不不不
Happy Thanksgiving.
感恩节快乐
Dad?
爸爸
Dad?! Are you there?!
爸爸  你在吗
Hello?!
有人吗
Dad.
爸爸
Dad? Please come in.
爸爸  进来
Don't do this to me!
别这么对我
It's more disappointment than anger.
我更多的是失望  而不是愤怒
You leave me no choice here, Kim.
你让我别无选择  金
You're out of control.
你失控了
This isn't permanent.
这不是永久的
It's not punishment.
这不是惩罚
I even left you some of the dinner,
我还给你留了晚饭
the holiday dinner we were supposed to have,
我们本来要一次吃的节日晚餐
including the pie,
包括派
which, frankly, you don't deserve.
老实说  不该给你吃的
That should tide you over for now.
你应该能好好想清楚
Your phone and your laptop are off-limits until you settle down.
在你安定下来之前  不得使用你的手机或电脑
Honey, I need to go out for a little bit,
亲爱的  我要出去一下
so we'll finish talking about this when I get back.
所以我们等我回来后再说这件事
Dad?
爸爸
Hey! You can't do this!
你不能这么做
Okay. Okay.
好吧
Fuck. Fuck!
操
Yes.
太好了
Kimberly.
金伯利
How did you do that?
你怎么做到的
Remember when I took you to that magic show when you were a kid?
你还记得我在你小时候带你去看的魔术表演吗
They made a woman disappear.
他们把一个女人变没了
Yeah. Remember, they locked her in a box, and poof!
记得吗  他们把她锁在盒子里
She was gone.
她就不见了
You leaned over to me,
你靠向我
you said, "Daddy, how'd they do that?"
问道  "爸爸  他们怎么做到的"
Remember what I said? Remember?
记得我怎么说的吗  记得吗
"It's magic.
"这是魔法
The woman will disappear for a bit,
那个女人会暂时消失
but she will always come out."
但是她永远会出来"
We spent the whole week playing hide-and-seek all over the house.
我们那一周都在屋子里玩捉迷藏
And you know what?
你知道吗
I always found you.
我总是能找到你
And you always came out.
你总是会出来
Please, come out.
出来吧
Right, then.
那好吧
Kimberly!
金伯利
Watch your ears, sweetheart.
捂上耳朵  亲爱的
Come on!
拜托
Just a little more, I'll be right there!
稍等一下  我马上来了
Oh, my God.
上帝啊
Jane? It's Henry.
简  我是亨利
Oh, I'm fine. Yeah, how are you?
我没事  你好吗
Uh, no, actually, right this second,
不  其实  她现在
she's in the middle of something.
正在忙
So, uh, hey, I could get her to call you back when she's finished.
我能等她忙完后让她打给你
- She called you? When? - Help!
-她给你打了电话  什么时候  -救命
- She is feeling a little cabin fever. - Help me!
-她有点患了幽居病  -救命
- So, that's a good sign, right? - Help me, please!
-这是好事  对吗  -救命
- Help! - I just think maybe
-救命  -我想她可能
- She was a little overzealous... - Help me!
-她非常想要  -救命
...about asking for a sleepover.
出去过夜
Absolutely, you should, yeah.
当然了  应该的
Kimberly would love to see you, you know.
金伯利很想见见你
Tell you what, give me a couple of days.
这样吧  给我几天
Honestly, the place is a mess.
说实在的  房子里现在一团糟
If I can just get the house in order.
让我把房子整理一下
Mm-hmm. Yeah, take care.
保重
Jesus fucking Christ.
我的上帝啊
So that was your Aunt Jane.
那是你的简阿姨
She said you had left a message. Something about making a trip?
她说你给了留言说要去她那儿什么的
You're not doing us any favors, honey.
你这样只会让我们越来越糟  亲爱的
Kim?
金
Oh, come on, do I have to come down in there and get you?
拜托  我得下来把你抓出去吗
Damn it!
该死
Kimberly?
金伯利
I know you're scared, Kim, but I don't think you get it.
我知道你很害怕  金  但我觉得你不明白
I'm trying to help you. I'm your father.
我是想帮你  我是你父亲
I love you.
我爱你
Doesn't matter what you did.
不管你做了什么
You're gonna remain completely quiet and do exactly as I say.
你要保持绝对安静  乖乖听我说的做
Otherwise, someone is gonna get hurt.
不然  有人就会受伤
Kimberly.
金伯利
Go.
上去
Dr. Saunders?
桑德斯医生
Hi. I'm sorry I'm running a bit late.
抱歉我有点迟到了
It's been a nightmare of a day.
今天真是像噩梦一样
There's all this post-holiday chaos and Black Friday mania.
节后的混乱和黑五的狂欢
I should have called and said I was running behind.
我应该打个电话告诉你我要迟到了
Are you okay?
你没事吧
What do you mean?
什么意思
Well, you look... dirty.
你看上去...很脏
Oh. Yeah, I've been working on the house.
是的  我一直在装修房子
May I come in?
我能进来吗
We're gonna have to reschedule, actually.
我们得换个时间了
Yeah, I got a lot of work to do,
我有很多活要干
and it's not a good time right now.
现在不是时候
Dad?
爸爸
It's okay.
没事
She can come in.
她可以进来
I don't think it's a good idea right now.
我觉得现在这不是一个好主意
Dr. Saunders came all this way.
桑德斯医生大老远的过来
It's fine.
没事的
We could finish up later, right?
我们可以待会儿再搞定  对吧
Okay.
好吧
- Oh, wow, you weren't kidding. - Yeah.
-你还真没开玩笑  -没错
Looks like a bomb went off in here.
这里好像刚刚爆炸过
Yeah, it's kind of a rough day.
是啊  今天真是忙坏了
Um, better in here today.
今天去那里吧
Okay.
好吧
Well, it's a good thing your dad's keeping you busy, though.
你爸爸总给你事情做也挺好的吧
Yeah.
嗯
Uh, listen, I'm gonna sit in on this one.
听着  今天我就在这旁听吧
If that's okay with you.
如果你不介意的话
Okay.
好吧
So, um, are you still taking your medication?
你还在服用你的药吗
No.
不
Why not?
为什么
I guess I forgot.
我想我忘了
Then how are you feeling without it?
那你不吃药感觉怎么样
My head's clearer.
我的脑袋更清楚了
And have the panic attacks, have they increased or decreased?
恐慌发作更加频繁还是有所减少
I don't know, sometimes I feel trapped.
我不知道  有时我感觉自己被困住了
Trapped?
被困住了
In this house.
困在这房子里
Not literally.
不是字面上的意思
How so?
为什么
Like I want to get out,
就像我想要出去
but I can't.
但我做不到
Okay. What's holding you back?
好吧  是什么拦住了你
I don't know what will happen to my dad.
我不知道我爸爸会怎么样
So you're afraid if you leave, you might not see your dad again?
你担心如果你离开  可能就再也见不到你爸爸吗
More like I won't come back.
更像是我再也不会回来了
Well, that's called growing up, Kim.
这就叫长大  金
And it happens to all of us eventually.
我们最后都会经历这一步
Children leave.
孩子们会离开
But one step at a time.
但是一步一步来
Let's just get you out the front door first, okay?
我们先让你走出前门吧  好吗
I never offered you a drink.
我从来没给你什么喝的
Oh, no, I'm fine. Thank you.
不用  我没事  谢谢
No, no, no, I make a great cup of tea.
不不不  我泡的茶很好
And my Aunt Jane, she's my mom's sister,
我的简阿姨  她是我妈妈的妹妹
just sent me these new teas to try,
给我寄了一些新茶叶
and I like to mix them together and make my own.
我想全部混在一起  做我的特制茶
I've got Lady Grey, Black Currant.
我有伯爵夫人茶   黑加仑茶
Kinda like Black Grey, you know?
有点像伯爵红茶  你知道吗
- Kim, she's fine. - Are you sure?
-金  她不要  -你确定吗
Stop pushing.
别逼她了
You know what? Um, yes.
好吧  我要
Yes, I would like to try the famous Kimberly Tooms brew.
我要  我想试试著名的金伯利・图姆斯茶
Great.
太好了
I will go make that now.
我现在就去做
Unless you'd like to make it.
除非你想去做
No.
不
Dr. Saunders would like a Kim special.
桑德斯医生想要金特制茶
I can make you one too if you want.
你想要的话我可以给你也泡一杯
Sure. Just don't take too long.
好  别花太久就行
- Everything okay in there? - Fine.
-一切都好吧  -很好
How was Thanksgiving?
感恩节过得怎么样
Okay, there we go.
好了
Thank you.
谢谢
Which one is this?
这杯是什么
Uh, I chose the Keemun,
我选了祁门红茶
with a pinch of the White Rose.
加了点白玫瑰
It could suck.
可能会不好喝
It's black tea, so just, you know, milk and sugar.
这是红茶  所以只有牛奶和糖
Think the milk turned.
我觉得牛奶坏了
I think it's lovely. I see what all the fuss is about.
我觉得很好喝  我明白为什么要大费周章了
I want to talk about my mom.
我想谈谈我妈妈
All right. Um, we can certainly do that, if you feel up to it.
好  当然可以了  如果你想的话
I do.
我想
Maybe we could take our time with that.
也许我们可以慢慢来
Uh, if Kimberly wants to talk about that, it's her choice.
如果金伯利想要谈  那这是她的选择
She can go wherever she wants to in these sessions.
她在治疗过程中想说什么都行
I do want to talk about it.
我想谈
Go ahead.
说吧
I've been thinking about it a lot lately.
我最近想了很多
You know, about what happened to her, and the man--
关于她的遭遇  还有那个
the man who killed her.
那个杀死她的人
I thought a lot about what I would say to him
我想过很多如果我有机会的话
if I ever had the chance.
我会对他说什么
And what would that be?
你要说什么呢
I wouldn't ask him why.
我不会问他为什么
No.
不
I know why.
我知道为什么
He did it because he's sick.
他这么做因为他是个变态
Because he enjoys it.
因为他很享受
He probably justifies it to himself.
他也许会给自己找理由
A man like that invents excuses to do what he does.
那种人会为自己的所作所为找任何借口
To excuse his own sickness.
解释他的病态
Remember you first told me that I was in a cocoon?
你还记得你第一次告诉我我是在一个茧里吗
Like a butterfly struggling to get out?
就像一只挣扎的蝴蝶
Maybe he's in a cocoon, too.
也许他也在茧里
Except... he hides in his,
只不过  他躲在他的茧里
where it's dark...
那里黑暗
where no one can see him
没人能看到
for what he really is.
真正的他
And I'd tell him he's a monster and a coward.
我会告诉他  他是个禽兽  懦夫
And what do you think he would say to you?
你觉得他会对你说什么
I'm afraid that's all the time we have for today.
恐怕今天就到此为止了
So much work to do around the house.
房子里还有很多活要干
Sorry, Doctor.
抱歉  医生
Right. Well, um,
嗯
I think we were breaking new ground here, Kimberly.
我觉得我们今天有新的突破  金伯利
Um, maybe at our next session, we can venture outside
也许下一次治疗  我们可以出门
maybe into the yard?
也许能去院子里
I'd like that.
我很愿意
Great job with the tea.
你的茶很棒
Five stars.
五星好评
Well, thank you, Doctor.
谢谢你  医生
Um... I actually need to ask you both something.
其实我要问你们俩一些事
- What's that? - I got a call last night
-什么事  -我昨晚接到电话
from an Officer Banks, I believe?
是一名叫班克斯的警官
She said they were called to this address.
她说这个地址有人报警
She wanted to confirm that I was Kimberly's doctor.
她想确认我是不是金伯利的医生
Is there anything I should know?
有什么事要告诉我吗
- No. - No.
-没有  -没有
No.
没有
All right.
好吧
- Oh, um, have a good weekend. - Thank you.
-周末愉快  -谢谢
Okay.
好
You are in so much trouble!
你麻烦大了
You wanted to know.
你那么想知道
Now you know.
现在你知道了
I'm gonna have to get rid of her, Kim.
我要处理掉她  金
I don't like to work like this.
我不喜欢这样干活
I like to be careful, precise, no traces.
我喜欢小心  精确  不留痕迹
These girls need to be punished.
这些女孩需要被惩罚
I can't let them influence you.
我不能让她们影响到你
I can't risk you being exposed to what they are.
我不能让你暴露在她们的影响下
I protect you, Kim.
我是在保护你  金
You know that, right?
你知道的  对吗
That's my purpose on earth, to make it safer for you.
这就是我在这世上的目的  为了保护你的安全
For when you come out of your cocoon.
等你从你的茧里出来
Upon emerging from its chrysalis,
从蛹中出来时
the butterfly is at its most vulnerable state in its life cycle.
蝴蝶处于其生命周期中最脆弱的阶段
Until that's done, it can't fly.
在那之前  它飞不了
And then it's easy prey for birds and other predators.
它只会成为鸟和其他捕食者的猎物
Your mother never understood that.
你的妈妈从来不理解
But then again, she never helped us
不过  她也从来没帮助过我们
with your fifth-grade science fair project, either, did she?
完成你的五年级科学项目  是吗
Second place. So proud.
第二名  多么自豪
But then when she found out...
但是当她发现...
yeah, it was like trying to put broken glass back together.
这简直就像把破碎的玻璃杯拼回起来
What was I supposed to do?
我能怎么办
She was just gonna tell the cops,
她只会告诉警察
and then they'd take you away from me forever.
然后他们就会永远地带走你
I never did anything but love you.
我只是爱你而已
I did the best I could under the circumstances.
我已经尽可能做到更好了
Do you not have anything to add?
你不想说些什么什么吗
You don't want to take a little personal responsibility for this?
你不想负点责任吗
You did this. This is your fault, Kimberly.
是你干的  这都是你的错  金伯利
Dr. Saunders would still be alive
如果你能乖乖听话
if you just did as you were told.
桑德斯医生现在还能活着
But you couldn't do it. You couldn't toe the line.
但你就是做不到  你没法遵守
And now this is where we are.
现在变成这样
If you act like a child, you'll be treated like one.
如果你总是像个孩子一样  你只会被当孩子
I'm not a bad man. Not at all.
我不是坏人  根本不是
One day, you're gonna walk out that door,
总有一天  你会走出那扇门
and you'll get that I made the world a safer place for you.
你会明白  我为你让这个世界更加安全
These girls...
这些女孩
these women, they all want you to...
这些女人  都想要你...
Well, just want you to be like them.
要你和她们一样
Even if you haven't met them,
就算你没见过她们
their influence, their energy, it's out there.
她们的影响  她们的能量  都在外面
And I would never allow that.
我绝对不会允许
Ever.
永远
You're my girl.
你是我的小女儿
The best thing I ever did.
我拥有过最好的东西
I always did everything for...
我永远会为你
for you.
做一切
F-For us.
为我们
Fuck you.
操你妈的
Hey... you just...
你刚刚
Kim...
金
Propofol.
异丙酚
Oh, yes. Okay.
太好了
Fuck, come on.
操  拜托
Okay.
好了
Pick up, pick up.
快接  快接
Cell phone ringing.
电话响了
Is that Tim O'Day calling?
是提姆・奥贝利吗
Oh, my God, what if it is?
天呐  万一真的是呢
Banks. Hello?
我是班克斯  你好
Yeah. Hi, it's Kimberly Tooms.
你好  我是金伯利・图姆斯
Remember, you said to call--
你记得吗  你说要是
to call you if something bad happened?
要是发生了什么事  就给你打电话
Yeah, I remember.
我记得
It's my Dad. You have to come now, okay?
是我爸爸  你得赶紧过来
You have to take him away.
你们得把他抓起来
- Has he hurt you? - He killed her.
-他伤害你了吗  -他杀了她
Sophie Taylor? You know, the missing girl from the TV?
索菲・泰勒  电视上失踪的那个女孩
I think he's killed other girls.
我觉得他还杀了其他人
I mean, he killed my therapist right in front of me.
他在我面前杀死了我的治疗师
Am I hearing you right?
我没听错吧
You're telling me your dad killed somebody in front of you?
你说你爸爸在你面前杀了人
- Yes. - Okay, where's your dad now, Kimberly?
-是的  -你爸爸现在在哪里  金伯利
Um, he's... he's passed out on the floor.
他  他在地板上晕倒了
I drugged him.
我给他下药了
But I don't know how much longer it's going to last.
但是我不知道能持续多久
Okay, I just need you to get out of the house immediately, okay?
我需要你现在马上离开那幢房子
I don't know if I can, okay?
我不知道我行不行
He boarded everything up. I'm locked in.
他把所有东西都藏了起来  我被锁在这里了
Stay on the line, okay?
不要挂  好吗
- What is it? - That domestic from the other night.
-怎么回事  -那晚的报警电话
Kimberly Tooms?
金伯利・图姆斯
She said her father's the one that killed Sophie Taylor.
她说是她父亲杀死了索菲・泰勒
Fuck!
操
- Kim, you still with me? -Yes.
-金  你还在吗  -嗯
Kimberly, I need you to get out of the house
金伯利  我需要你赶紧离开房子
and get as far away as you possibly can, okay?
跑的越远越好  行吗
We've go units on the way, okay? Can you hear me?
我们的警察在路上了  你听到了吗
Yeah, look, I lied yesterday.
我昨晚撒谎了
Something's wrong.
的确有事
Oh, shit.
该死
Kim?
金
He's--
他
Kimberly--
金伯利
You didn't use enough for someone my size.
你下的药不足以麻倒我这体型
But the White Rose tea was very soothing.
但是白玫瑰茶很棒
God damn it, I fucking love you! How do I prove that?!
该死  我真的爱你  我要怎么证明
Go to hell!
去死吧
You're not goin' anywhere!
你哪里都别想去
This is our home!
这是我的家
I called the police!
我报警了
I told them everything.
我什么都告诉他们了
They're gonna come, and they're gonna lock you up this time.
他们马上来了  这次他们会把你抓起来
There's no more hiding, Dad.
不要再躲了  爸爸
I--
我...
Ohh, Look what you did to our family!
看看你对我们家庭都做了什么
Look what you did to it!
看看你都做了什么
So stupid!
多么愚蠢
Stupid!
愚蠢
We can fix this.
我们可以解决的
Oh, no.
不
Dad.
爸爸
Dad, no.
爸爸  不
Aah! Oh, my God!
天啊
Dad, stop!
爸爸  住手
Dad, what are you doing?!
爸爸  你在干什么
Stop!
住手
Dad, please don't do this.
爸爸  不要这样
Please don't do this.
拜托不要这样
- I got these... - Dad, please don't do this.
-这些是...  -爸爸  不要这么做
...for your birthday candles.
你的生日蜡烛
Stop. Please don't.
住手  不要这样做
That goddamn necklace.
那该死的项链
I lied!
我撒谎了
I never called the police.
我从来就没有报警
You didn't?
你没有吗
No. I made that up.
是的  我编的
They're not coming.
他们不会来的
Okay? You're safe.
好吗  你很安全
You're safe here.
你很安全
Oh, sweetheart.
亲爱的
You look so much like your mother.
你看上去真像你的妈妈
I'm sorry, Daddy.
对不起  爸爸
Aah! Kimberly?!
金伯利
How many times have I told you to pick up after yourself?!
我和你说了多少次得自己收拾
Okay, okay.
好了  好了
I'm having a...
我今天
just a really, really bad day.
过得非常非常糟心
I could use a little understanding here.
我需要一些理解
You're my daughter.
你是我的女儿
We're supposed to look after each other.
我们应该互相照应
You're a smart girl, lots of potential.
你很聪明  潜力很大
I know I said a lot of things today and...
我知道我今天说了很多话
some hurtful things. I know that.
有些很伤人  我知道
But through everything,
但是尽管如此
I have never been prouder of you.
我还是如此为你自豪
You've done so well, sweetheart.
你做得很好  亲爱的
You used to hide up here all the time.
你以前经常会躲在这里
So cute.
很可爱
I'm not hiding now.
我现在不躲了
So come and get me.
来抓我吧
That's my girl.
这才乖嘛
Okay.
好
Fuck!
操